BERNARDO ZELAYA

PROFILE



+5493814455130



Bernardo_zelaya@hotmail.com



Bernardo Zelaya



github.com/zelayab



bzpage.netlify.app



Programmer with excellent qualities of creativity and functionality. Effective and agile management in terms of learning and performance, with the ability to work in a team

I have been working with Angular for 1 year on a large-scale project, in which we use Typescript, Sass, and also version control through GIT. For the different tasks we manage Jira and Confluence, together with the Microsoft Team and Slack for communications. At the same time I'm currently doing personal projects in React.

SKILLS



















TRAINING

2019 - 2020

Curso #Yopuedoprogramar avalado por el Ministerio de modernización – Ministerio de desarrollo – Microsoft Curso de CODE.ORG sobre demostración y entendimiento de los conceptos básicos de Ciencias de la computación. "The Hour of Code"

Curso CodoACodo programación

Curso POLOTIC de Front End HTML Y CSS

Curso Google Activate – Introduccion al desarrollo web I y II.

Curso POLOTIC Ingles para desarrolladores

Curso CTC Cluster JAVASCRIPT

Curso CTC Cluster React

2021

Bootcamp Node Js - Incluit 2021 Curso ComIT Node JS - 2021 Cursando Tecnicatura en programacion - UTN - 2021

Cursando Tecnicatura en programacion - UTN -Hackathon Gentleman Programming - 2021

EXPERIENCE

2019 - Current

KUMO -

Creation of web pages using HTML, CSS, JS and Wordpress

2021 - 2022

INCLUIT -

Frontend Developer

Project: Coca-Cola B2B - shopping cart

2022 - Current

Qubik Digital

Front Developer / SAP Spartacus

COLLEGE

2021

Technician in programming - UTN - National Technological University